Mohamad Fadel

Web Developer | Jakarta,Indonesia | +6283894535352 | mohamad.fadel196@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamad-fadel-12a251194/

PROFILE

Hi there, i'm Fadel from Indonesia. Experience in Analyzing, Designing, Developing and Integrating Front-End & Back-End based applications. Experience in developing applications using NodeJs Services, and Restful Web Services. Experience in developing web applications using HTML, CSS,SASS, JavaScript, ReactJS, and NextJs. and accustomed to working using SDLC and Agile methods in developing a website.

EDUCATION

Gunadarma University

Bachelor of Information Technology (S.Kom), Sep 2015 – Dec 2019

GPA: 3,06

• **Concentration**: Information Technology.

• Relevant Coursework: Basic Logical IT, Analytical Business Plan, Database Management System.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer, PT. Astra International Tbk., DKI Jakarta

June 2020 - Present

- Create and develop the front view of the website based on the design of the UI/UX team that will be displayed and used by the user.
- Create and develop content management system (CMS) to make it easier for the operations team to change or adjust the appearance of the website without having to know programming.
- Manage website, user experience, design, and bussines flow.
- Connects to the api backend data which will be used to be displayed to the front visible to the user.
- Developed and implemented React Components using NextJs.
- Creating appropriate integration strategies with client side components and APIs.
- Troubleshooting layout and functional issues across multiple browsers and device.
- Implementing and maintaining scalable front end architecture utilizing latest javascript/typescript libraries and framework.
- Utilizing industry best practices for mobile-first and responsive web design.
- Working with version control systems and source code management tools (e.g GIT,SVN) to keep track of code.
- Collaborating with UX teams to create interactive applications and websites.
- Developing user-friendly web pages and features to effectively optimize user experience.
- Impelementing web accessibility standards and developing suitable web content for all browsers, platforms, and devices.

Seva ID (Astra International)

Web Developer | June 2020 - April 2021

- Develop new web interface features for users.
- Generate reusable code making permits to various relevant stakeholders.
- Create and manage web content management system (CMS).
- Implemented and maintained front end web applications.

Meta By Astra (Astra International)

Web Developer | April 2021 - Present

- Develop new web interface features for users.
- Generate reusable codem making permits to various relevant stakeholders.
- Create and manage web content management system (CMS).
- Implemented and maintained front end web applications.

Natacara ID (Astra International)

Fullstack Developer | April 2021 - January 2023

- Develop new web interface features for users.
- Generate reusable codem making permits to various relevant stakeholders.
- Create and manage web content management system (CMS).

SKILLS & TECH

· Technical Skills:

Javascript, Sass, RestApi, Html, React, GraphQl, Bootstrap, Css, NextJs, Mysgl, Typescript, Git.

Soft Skills :

Great Communication, Agile, Scrum, Problem Solving, TeamWork, Willingness To Learn

LANGUAGES

- Bahasa | Native
- English | Competent

CERTIFICATION

- Sql Server Project (Gunadarma University)
- Oracle for Intermediate (Gunadarma University)
- Sql Server for intermediate (Gunadarma University)
- Sql Server for beginner (Gunadarma University)